♪ it seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ is violence in movies
and sex on tv ♪
♪ but where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ on which we used to rely? ♪
♪ lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ lucky there's a man who
positively can do ♪
♪ all the things that make us ♪
♪ laugh and cry ♪
♪ he's... A...
Fam... Ily... Guy! ♪
Good morning, family.
Now, as you all know,
since four minutes ago,
When I heard it on the radio,
It has been my lifelong dream
To compete in the st. Philip's
greasy pole contest,
Where shirtless men try
to climb across a greasy pole.
Come on, chris, let's go.
Now, hold on, peter,
you promised
You'd run errands with me today.
You can't just bail 'cause
you heard of some fun new thing.
Lois, we both know I'm going to
the whatever-I-just-said thing.
Meg will fill in for me.
Ugh, fine.
All right, now, if you're
gonna be filling in for me,
You need to complete
the online course.
Congratulations on being picked
to fill in for me
While I have a horse-around day.
Now, let's talk dos and don'ts
around the workplace.
Okay, let's see what
you've learned.
Describe the difference between
a tunic and a shawl
In as much detail as possible.
Ugh.
Congratulations on being
picked...
Every year there's some hotshot
who thinks
They don't gotta watch
the video.
Oh, no, I left my phone
in the car.
Oh, weird. I forgot mine, too.
Should I run back and grab them?
-Oh, we don't need 'em.
-No, we do not.
I for one welcome
the lost art of conversation,
Of which we are both ninjas,
my friend.
Absolutely.
♪ bah dah buh buh ba ♪
♪ bah dah buh buh da dah! ♪
So, how you doing, man?
All good. All good in the hood.
Anything new? What's new?
Same old, same old.
Life good? Family good?
Yep, living the dream.
D-r-e-a-m. No complaints.
Zero complaints.
Dylan, right? Your son. He good?
Most def.
[cell phone alerts chiming]
-Breaking news.
-I can't believe this.
I have a samsung, so my alert
hasn't come in yet.
It's nice not being glued
to our phones
Like these sheeple, huh?
[samsung phone chimes]
[man] there it is. Oh, my god.
Slaves to the screen.
Are we almost done?
I need to find
stewie's rash cream,
But if you're not having fun,
go get a squeeze
From the blood pressure machine.
That always perks me up.
[phone chiming]
Meg, oh, my god,
it's crazy here.
Dad fell off the pole
and landed on his head,
And one of his eyes popped out.
We picked it up
and jammed it back in,
But the pupil was
on the other side.
I'm okay.
Just got a little headache.
Also, dad gave me
a hard lemonade.
He's pretty out of it.
Total shocker,
chris and dad are having
A very fun day.
They're not the only ones, huh?
Oh, I also need to return
this loofah.
I mean, who was I kidding?
I'm a dial bar
-Smeared right on the skin gal.
-Of course.
Let me show you
to the returns section.
[explosion]
[mort]
the prestige.
Well, I guess janet
forgave robert for jamaica.
-What are you talking about?
-The wedding's back on.
And janet officially has
no backbone.
What are you doing?
Um, eating a sandwich.
Brian griffin,
I ordered ramen for us.
We planned this last night.
We did?
I don't-- I don't remember.
You were too drunk to remember?
I've been dying
to try this place.
You said we could
do it together.
-Stewie, it's not--
-[knock on door]
Uh, ramen for stewie and brian?
Apparently it's just for stewie.
-Everything okay?
-No, it's not!
[sobbing]
Stewie, what the hell was that?
What happened to us?
I thought we were best friends.
We have nothing to say
at brunch,
We don't listen to each other,
we forget plans we made.
By the way, the
"we" in all this is you.
Don't be dramatic,
stewie, we're fine.
No, we're not.
Best friends talk about stuff.
I-I don't--
what do you want me to do?
If you're really asking,
I saw a therapist
On the today show talking about
The emergence of
friendship therapy.
I think it could help us.
-No.
-[crying]
-[sighs] fine.
-Oh, brian, this is great.
It'll give us
the fresh start we need.
Like when tom brady
moved to tampa bay.
All right!
Now I get to cheat in shorts.
I'm peyton manning,
and I approve this message.
So, yeah, this is how I reload
my purse with mom stuff.
-It's very important
to always be prepared.
-Didn't ask.
Travel-size lotion,
hand sanitizer,
Tic tacs, so I can
skip brushing my teeth.
Dawg, you still gotta brush.
Oh, and mom hack 68:
Buy the $2.00
plastic rain bonnet.
They're made at the same factory
that makes the $9.00 ones.
Don't ask me how I know.
Oh, meg, don't look for a sec.
Okay, it's safe.
Our treat for an epic
errands day.
Amazing.
Big surprise, I didn't win.
Didn't win what?
Oh, my god, meg, I won!
You're kidding.
Mom, this is amazing.
Ah! I know, I can't believe it.
It's even more exciting than
the creation of broccolini.
What is this new plant?
Let me ask you a question.
-Do you like broccoli?
-Not really.
Well, I think I just figured out
a way to make it harder to eat.
I can't believe
you won ten grand.
I know. I wonder how soon
I can get that
House water filtration system
installed.
A couple weeks? A month?
-What is wrong with you?
-Wh-what do you mean?
You win a boatload of money,
and your first thought is
A water filtration system?!
How do you not
blow your brains out?
Oh, these systems are very cool.
No, they're not! They're boring.
Everything you do is boring.
That's why we all want
to hang out with dad.
Imagine what he'd do
with ten grand.
Something super stupid
and selfish and awesome,
That's what.
-Dad's not the only
fun one, you know.
-Uh-huh?
Oh, you don't believe me?
Okay, okay.
Well, what if--
what if we use the money
For something fun? For just us.
-Like what?
-Like going on a top-secret
-Mother/daughter trip.
-Really?
Mom, that would be amazing.
Great. Now let's keep
this same energy
While we take a quick detour
for my mammogram.
Whoo-hoo! Girls' trip!
How's it looking in there?
Well, it's probably nothing.
[weakly]
ooh, girls' trip.
[man over p.A.] final call
for vacation airlines flight
To vacation destination.
I can't believe we're
going on a secret trip.
This is so cool.
What did you tell dad?
Oh, pfft, he won't even know
we're gone.
I got him
his favorite babysitter.
Lois says we're allowed
to stay up past 9:00.
The note says 9:00.
Not if it's special.
And we're allowed
to watch beetlejuice.
The note specifically says
"no beetlejuice."
I'm allowed to watch coco,
And it's basically
the same thing.
I'm dr. Wagner.
Please take a seat.
This is a test, right?
You're free to sit
anywhere you like.
Yeah? This right?
There's no right or wrong.
Aha, you lost.
You sat too quick.
Are you uncomfortable
that brian had the confidence
-To choose a seat?
-Yes!
Brian one, stewie zero.
Actually, brian,
this isn't a contest.
Yes. One to one.
Stewie, please sit.
I may just stand.
Oh, indecisive. Two to one.
Doc's going pen to pad,
and you gotta think
Stewie just evened up the score.
It does look like we have
an ocean-view suite available
For an extra $500
if you are interested.
You know what, yes,
we'll take it.
The snapple babes are
living it up.
Very good.
So the room isn't quite ready.
Would you like to inconveniently
Grab your swimsuits
from your luggage
And use the pool while you wait?
Oh, that's okay,
we'll just buy new bathing suits
At the lobby store.
[all gasp]
Snapple babes?
And for our survey,
How'd you hear about the resort?
That rich lady from the news
was murdered here.
Yep, that is what
most people say.
Hey, stewie,
what are you watching?
-Uh, uh, the gilded age.
-Seriously?!
I couldn't wait, I'm sorry.
I'll watch it again
with you tonight.
Oh, and have you stare at me
right before
Something big happens? No way.
You know what,
you know what, good.
I'll watch shows on my own, too.
I can finally watch something
after 7:00 p.M.
Dr. Wagner would want us to play
big problem, small problem.
A big problem is sometimes
a hospital problem.
A small problem is
something like
Your friend watches a show--
I'm not listening to this crap.
This is stupid.
You feel like this is stupid?
Dr. Wagner says to use
"I feel" statements.
I feel like you are
making up rules--
Oh, stewie's got the ipad.
Stewie, daddy's just gonna
take the ipad
Into the bathroom, okay?
He took my etch a sketch.
[peter]
siri, show me "busty latinas."
Busty latinas.
Can somebody reset the wi-fi?
-Have you decided?
-Yes.
We'd like two lava flows
in hollowed-out pineapples,
And sweet potato fries
in a hollowed-out coconut.
Any food or drink you bring us
Should be inside
a hollow fruit.
Excuse me, my son and I
couldn't help but notice
You ordered all your food
in hollowed-out fruit.
You must be very rich.
Oh, thanks for noticing.
So what are your names?
You can call us
the snapple babes.
[chuckles] yeah, we're famous.
Well, maybe you can tell us
All about it over dinner.
Shall we say one of
the three overpriced
Hotel restaurants at 8:00?
-[chuckles] we shall.
-See you then.
I forgot these are prescription,
But those are two
smokin'-hot blobs.
So, last session
I asked you each
To write a love song
to your friendship.
Let's start with brian.
Whatever. [clears throat]
♪ stewie, stewie ♪
♪ oh, yeah ♪
♪ awesome guy. ♪
What the hell was that?
You couldn't be bothered
To spend five minutes
preparing something?
Like it matters.
This is so stupid.
You're stupid!
[grunting, straining]
Guys, please.
Admit you exaggerate
your accent.
Admit you wear shirts from
museums you've never been to.
Enough!
This is ridiculous.
Your relationship is toxic.
You're not married,
you're not blood relatives.
Why continue?
[inhales deeply]
In my entire career,
I have never given this advice,
but it is my opinion
That you should end
this friendship.
-Fine by me.
-Makes my life easier.
Also, your insurance card
didn't go through,
And when I looked again
I realized
It was a robek's juice card.
You went to suny albany.
You'll take it and like it.
Okay, this is
a bartering culture,
So we have to haggle over
an amount of money
We wouldn't even pick up
if we dropped it on the ground.
[both gasp, yelp]
[both grunting]
[tires squealing]
[meg]
mom, what are they gonna do
with us?
[lois]
if you let my daughter go,
You can do whatever you want
to me.
In the following order:
You, you, blond-arm-hair guy,
You two,
maybe a quick lunch and shower,
Then blond-arm-hair guy again
if he's into it.
♪ ♪
[gasps]
you two?
Where are we?
It's a co-kidnapping space.
It used to be a wework.
Oh, I saw that documentary.
Meh.
Sorry to interrupt.
Is there, like, a trick
to the keurig machine?
Hey, man. Yeah,
it's probably just out of water.
God, there's nothing in here.
Where's the money?
Uh, I'd look in the lobby store.
Ah, guilty as charged. [laughs]
No, but they do have fun stuff
in there.
Shut up! The real money will
be the ransom, anyways.
We've never captured
a beverage heiress before.
What?! Who do you think we are?
We know
you're the snapple family.
[laughing]
oh, no.
This is a big misunderstanding.
We just won a snapple contest,
then spent all the money.
[scoffs]
you're worthless!
[mechanical whirring]
[kidnapper]
it was the water.
[string instruments playing]
And do you, janet, take robert
to be your husband?
I do.
...Forgive you about jamaica.
[chuckles softly]
am I right?
Brian, what are you doing here?
I should ask you that.
Can't believe you came,
knowing I'd be here.
Well, I'm not gonna punish janet
for what happened between us.
Okay,
but just keep your distance.
Fine, I get from the bar
To the bridesmaid
having a terse, ugly argument
With her boyfriend.
Okay, and I get from her
To the bald uncle looking around
before telling a racist joke.
So, how long we thinking
Until stewie makes
this whole event about him?
Ten minutes? Shall we put
a little cashish on it?
I just asked you
to pass the butter.
I don't know who stewie is.
Do yourself a favor,
keep it that way.
I think we're supposed to sit
at the tables we were assigned.
Yeah, no, they said
I could kind of be a roamer.
[sniffs]
smells like butt.
Let me guess.
Brian was just here?
-Who's brian?
-I think that's the dog guy.
I thought this table was just
supposed to be cornell people.
Oh, my god.
Mom, we're gonna die.
Oh, no, we're not.
I have a plan.
Uh, hey, guys,
you know, if you're hungry,
I have a half a granola bar
in my purse.
This purse is useless,
just like you!
Huh. The good people
At t.J. Maxx may disagree
with you there.
[grunts]
[grunting]
-[grunts]
-huh?
[both grunt]
[panting]
[screaming]
-[man grunts]
-[lois screams]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[both grunting]
-Good day.
Both men:
Good day.
It was them
in the nine-dollar rain bonnets!
Told you these look
like the expensive ones.
[meg gasps]
[groans]
Never mess with a mom.
Meg, help me tie up their hands
With these extremely long
cvs receipts.
Why did you save these?
Oh, there's
a carpet-cleaning coupon
On the back
that I'm curious about.
[upbeat,
instrumental rock playing]
I'd like to invite
all the single ladies
To the dance floor!
[screaming]
How about the single fellas?
[cheering, whooping]
Now, some slowly-building
emotional music
For estranged friends
to look at each other
And regret their rift!
[playing slow, gentle music]
Ah. What are we doing?
[microphone feedback squeals]
Hey, I, uh, have a toast.
[clears throat]
You know, sometimes,
against all odds,
Two people find each other
In this crazy place
we call "earth."
Sure, they might have problems,
And they might not always agree
with each other,
And a therapist may even tell
them they shouldn't be friends.
But what I realized is
I don't want a friend
I can get along with.
I can get along with anybody.
[man]
table two hates you, dude!
I want a friend who I can laugh
with because they also noticed
That no one else
is drinking cream soda,
Which means the guy in jeans
brought it from home.
I knew they wouldn't have it!
I want a friend
Who will publicly shame
a mom-and-pop cafe
For having slightly too few
blueberries in their muffin.
[stewie]
call it something else,
'cause it ain't
a blueberry muffin.
Stewie, this is for you.
[playing upbeat rock tune]
♪ stewie, stewie ♪
♪ oh, yeah,
you're my best friend! ♪
He did the work.
Stewie, I'd rather be toxic
and unhealthy together
Than toxic and unhealthy apart.
Me, too, bri.
Let's be best friends again.
What do you say
we hit the photo booth
And take a couple
of funny photos?
I've heard
they have hilarious props.
-No props.
-Yeah, no props, yeah.
[cleveland]
but stewie did use props,
And they had a big fight
about it,
And it took
a whole other wedding
For them to make up again.
I'm cleveland brown,
And I know
my show was better than this.
I can't believe
we made it home safe.
It was so lucky you had
all that stuff in your purse.
Oh, sweetie,
luck had nothing to do with it.
I'm a mom, and moms have
to be prepared for anything.
I really wanted to show you
I could be fun like dad,
But look where that got us.
At the end of the day,
Someone's got
to be the responsible one here.
I guess you're right, mom.
I mean, we all love your
father's water balloon fights,
But someone's got to pick up
all the tiny balloon pieces
From the grass.
That's my role, and it's fine.
Do you think
someday I'll be a boring,
Taken-for-granted wife and mom?
Oh, I think you're well
on your way, sweetheart.
Oh. How was he?
Fine, but let's just say
There's the exact same number
of carrots as when you left.
Well, that sounds about right.
He also said you said
Yogurt-covered pretzels
are a healthy snack.
-[lois sighs]
-[peter] you did say that!
-Compared to cheetos, they are.
-You just said it again!
[clicking, whooshing]
-Here are your waffles.
-Thanks so much.
Yay, that was quick.
[phones whooshing]
Can I grab anything else
for you?
-No, this is great!
-Cheat day!
♪ ♪